非常好，做完之后，需要把所有需要的
Alright, you're done. Let's start by adding all of
字符串添加在新的偏好设置中。
the strings we're going to need for our new preference.
Key，label，还有一些像true，false，和default。
Key, label, and something like true, false, and default.
然后我们将要添加一些额外的偏好在之前的通用xml里和
Then we'll additional preference into pref general xnl, a check
一些checkbox来对应我们所定义的这些设置项
box preference that uses those strings we just defined.
让我们来重新过一遍我们syncAdaptor。 在提示功能中，
Let's go over to our sync adaptor. In the notify
添加一些代码来获取偏好数据
function, we add the code to fetch the preference
并且使用这些数据。看，就是这样。
and make use of it. And there we have it.
现在消息提示不会再被显示了，如果用户不希望这样
Now we won't display notifications if the user doesn't want us
这对于一个应用是锦上添花的。
to, which is a great thing for an app to do.